

CONTACT

- **J** +2348134497699
- → abdurrashidrabiu94@gmail.com
- Kano, 700233, Nigeria
- in www.linkedin.com/in/abdurrash id-rabiu-886220208

SKILLS

JQUERY

CSS

HTML

PHP

JAVASCRIPT

LARAVEL

VUE JS

Abdurrashid Rabiu

Software Engineer

My name is Abdurrashid Rabiu Umar, I am from Nigeria, I graduated with a degree in Computer Science from Bayero University, Kano (B.U.K). I am a computer programmer and a full stack web developer with specialization in programming languages like PHP and JavaScript, I also work with frameworks like Laravel and Vue js, I know libraries like jQuery and Bootstrap and also other web technologies like AJAX, JSON, APIs and many more. I have a three years experience working with PHP, two years experience working with JavaScript, Bootstrap and Laravel, and one year experience working with jQuery and Vue js. I am a collaborative team player with excellent technical abilities.

EDUCATION

PGD Computer Science 2019-2020

Bayero University, Kano

B.Sc. Computer Science 2013-2018

Bayero University, Kano

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Web Developer

2020-Present

Salafwa Technologies Limited

Designed and develop efficient and maintainable software according to business objectives and needs of various clients.

Course Tutor

2019-2020

Intersystem Institute of Information Technology

I work with the above named institute as part of my National Youth Service Corp. (NYSC) program for a period of one year and I work as a tutor for the course "Computer Programming with Visual Basic".